There's a penis in front of me.
目の前におちんちんがありますけど
yes.
はい
Mine is a little different.
僕の、ちょっと違う
What should I do, you dick?
どうすか、このおちんちん
Look, look.
見て、見て
Look at your dick.
おちんちん見て
Smell it and see it.
匂い嗅いで見て
Do you smell it?
匂い嗅ぐんですか?
big.
大きい
big?
大きい?
It's already twitching.
もうピクピクしてんじゃん
Well, it's the penis of an acquaintance of mine.
でさ、 僕の知り合いのちんぽなんですけど、
I think it's scary to have a dick you don't know,
知らないちんぽだと怖いと思うんだけど、
I want this dick to feel good too.
このちんぽもさ、気持ちよくしてあげてほしいなと思って
yes.
はい
That's fine.
いいですよ
Can I lick it?
舐めていいですか?
difficult.
難しい
This dick is also sweet.
このちんぽも甘い
sweet?
甘い?
delicious?
おいしい?
delicious.
おいしい
Say it while eating?
食わえながら言う?
Can I eat it?
食わえていい?
Your dick is delicious.
おくちんぽおいしい
He asked me to release a lot of thick sperm and make my mouth and pussy pregnant.
濃い精子いっぱい出して、 お口まんこ妊娠させてくださいって
Please release a lot of thick sperm and make my mouth and pussy pregnant.
濃い精子いっぱい出して、 お口まんこ妊娠させてください
I think I'll go.
行 きそう
sorry.
すみません
Why were you so nervous?
なんでジュッとしてたの?
Sperm.
精子して
It's really dark though.
ほんとに濃いけど
Are you sure you're going to get pregnant?
ほんとに妊娠しちゃうんじゃない?
The mouth.
口は
It was a little dark.
ちょっと濃いった
Was it dark?
濃いった?
Yeah.
うん
lie?
嘘?
What does semen taste like?
精子はさ、どんな味してるの?
this.
これ
It was a little bitter.
ちょっと苦かった
Was it a little bitter?
ちょっと苦かった?
It was a little bitter.
ちょっと苦かった
Did you hate sperm?
精子嫌かった?
I hated it.
嫌かった
Thank you for giving me so much.
いっぱい出してくれて
Both?
どっちも?
Both.
どっちも
Thank you for giving me so much.
いっぱい出してくれてありがとうございます
Let's have a meal
ご ち そう
It was.
さ までした
It was hard to cum.
精子むしかったです